We've covered a lot of ground in this lesson.
我们在这一课中已经覆盖了很多
You've looked at a number of AWS services,
你看过一些 AWS 服务
a few of their abilities and importantly how
他们有几种能力更重要的是
these services can be made multi AZ or multi-region.
这些服务可以做成多个 AZ 或多区域
You've seen how server-based services and compute services
您已看到基于服务器的服务和计算服务
get spread out into multiple subnets which lead to multiple availability zones.
将其扩展至多个子网 这些子网将导致多个可用性区域
You've set up DynamoDB to work in a multi-region mode by working with
您已设置 DynamoDB 以在多区域方式下工作
global tables and you've used advanced features to manage your data in the multi AZ,
全局表 您已使用高级功能来管理多个 AZ中的数据
by default S3 service.
缺省 S3   S3 服务
Finally, you worked with AWS compute services to understand how
最后 您与 AWS 计算服务合作 了解如何
to take generic custom servers and run them redundantly as well.
以使用通用定制服务器 并以冗余方式运行这些服务器
You should now have a good handle on which
你现在应该好好处理
services are suitable for which type of redundancy needs.
服务适合哪种类型的冗余需求
You've also seen some of the built-in redundancy in AWS native services.
您还在 AWS 本机服务中看到了一些内置的冗余
Using this knowledge to select the appropriate services for your use case,
使用此知识为您的用例选择适当的服务
will save you a lot of time and effort
会为您节省大量的时间和精力
instead of trying to use the wrong tool for the job.
而不是用错误的工具来找工作
We've seen the basics of high availability in AWS and
我们在 AWS 中看到了高可用性的基础知识
now how to build a resilient application services.
现在如何构建弹性应用程序服务
Soon, we'll get to considering
很快我们就会考虑
our business goals and then observability and recoverability.
我们的业务目标和可观察性和可恢复性